welcome to category 5 technology TV
歡迎來到5類科技電視
episode number 444 for tuesday the 22nd
星期二22日第 444集
of March 2016 so nice to see ya i'm your
2016那麼好三月看看雅我是 你的
host ravi ferguson please help me
主持人 ravi ferguson請 幫幫我
welcome Shelley de Silva tonight we are
今晚我們歡迎Shelley de Silva
leaving retro gaming in the past and we
離開復古遊戲過去和我們
are going to fly to the future nice with
將要 飛向未來
virtual reality goggles from mcdonalds
來自麥當勞的虛擬現實護目鏡
what gonna show you all about it also
什麼要告訴你這一切 還
Nelson hudis is joining us tonight to
Nelson hudis今晚將加入我們
talk about what is brand new from net
從 網上談起什麼 是全新的
talk he'll be talking about da home
說他會談論da home
phone service devices for unlimited long
電話服務設備無限長
distance calling he's also going to be
距離呼喚他也將成為
introducing a new app and even 4G
推出新的應用甚至4G
cellular service so Nelson will tell us
蜂窩服務所以尼爾森會告訴我們
all about that coming up nice and let's
所有這些都很好，讓我們來吧
throw over to Jeff and see what's coming
扔到傑夫身上，看看會發生什麼
up in the news thanks so much guys
在新聞中感謝這麼多人
here's what's coming up in the category
這是類別中出現的內容
5 tvnewser scans of King Tut's tomb have
圖特墳墓的5次電視新聞掃描
revealed what could be hidden rooms or
透露了什麼可能是隱藏的房間或
possibly the long-lost burial tomb of
可能是久違的墓葬
Queen Nefertiti a recall notice for my
女王納芙蒂蒂為我的召回通知
key as reports come has come out that a
關鍵的報告來了，a
lamp could shock you Google's inbox can
燈可以震撼你谷歌的收件箱可以
now reply to your emails for you by the
現在回复你的電子郵件
way I taken over as many as 275 million
方式我接手了多達2.75億
Android phones are at risk thanks to a
由於a，Android手機面臨風險
new code execution exploit and big-name
新的代碼執行漏洞和大牌
sites have been hit by a rash of
網站遭到了一連串的打擊
malicious pads sending crypto ransomware
惡意墊發送加密勒索軟件
stick around the full details are coming
堅持全部細節即將到來
up later in the show this is category 5
在節目的後期，這是第5類
technology TV
科技電視
welcome back this is category 5
歡迎回來這是第5類
technology TV and I'm Ravi Ferguson hi
科技電視和我是Ravi Ferguson嗨
I'm Shelly hey Charlie hey it is time
我是雪莉嘿查理嘿，現在是時候了
for viewers to to jump on board with
讓觀眾跳上船
category 5 partner with us through our
5類通過我們與我們合作
patreon profile through paypal different
patreon配置文件通過paypal不同
ways that you can actually support
你可以真正支持的方式
category 5 TV patreon.com / category 5
5類電視patreon.com /類別5
is a really cool way to be able to
是一種非常酷的方式
support us because what you can say is
支持我們，因為你可以說是
ok I want to support category 5 TV for
好的， 我想支持5類電視
25 cents per episode which translates
每集25美分翻譯
into 25 cents per week so by doing that
通過這樣做，每週25美分
there's power in numbers and all it
數字和所有它都有力量
would take is one thousand viewers
需要的是一千名觀眾
viewers yeah so yourself included if you
觀眾耶，所以如果你自己包括在內
think you can do 25 cents per episode
認為你每集可以做25美分
1000 viewers and we would be able to
1000觀眾，我們將能夠
have all of our bills paid and anything
我們支付了所有賬單和任何東西
that's left over from ad revenue and
這是廣告收入遺留下來的
things like that we would be able to
那樣的話，我們就能夠
sink into making the shows better
沉淪使節目變得更好
improving the quality doing whatever it
提高質量做任何事情
is that we need to be able to do in
是，我們需要 能夠做的
order to get to the kind of to keep
為了得到那種 保持
going with category 5 so our bills are
與第5類一致，所以我們的賬單是
our primary focus yeah making sure the
我們的主要焦點是的，確保了
rent is paid we've got a beautiful
租金是我們有一個美麗的
studio here in Barrie Ontario we've got
工作室在巴利安大略省我們有
our internet service which is LTE
我們的互聯網服務是LTE
internet and it's been fairly reliable
互聯網，這是相當可靠的
we had a little bit of an outage a
我們有一點停電了
couple weeks ago well a full-out outage
幾個星期前完全停電
but otherwise it's been really really
但除此之外真的是真的
good since we moved into studio deal
好，因為我們搬進了工作室交易
good but our bills are high and we're
好，但我們的賬單很高，我們是
volunteers and we want to keep bringing
志願者，我們想繼續帶來
this thing to you so if you love what we
這件事對你來說如果你愛我們的話
do if you want to support us if you feel
如果你願意，如果你想支持我們的話
like hey I can do 25 cents per episode
嘿，我每集可以做25美分
please check out its patreon.com /
請查看 其patreon.com /
category 5 is the actual link and that
第5類是實際的鏈接
will show you how you can support us in
將告訴你如何支持我們
that way and learn a little bit more
這樣，學到 更多
about what it is that we're doing in
關於 我們正在做什麼
addition to category 5 technology TV and
除了 5類技術電視和
see how you can support us if you
看看你如何能夠支持我們
support us for as little as 25 cents per
支持我們每個只需25美分
episode 1 you're going to be entered
第1集你將被輸入
into a draw for a couple of teeny drones
為幾個小小的無人機畫一個平局
I can't do a race pack those are the
我不能做那些比賽
little micro quadcopters and we're going
小微型四軸，我們要去
to be qualifying you for some additional
有資格獲得一些額外的資格
contests and some additional things like
比賽和一些額外的事情，如
that and we're gonna be talking about
那我們要談論的
some contests a little bit later on
一些比賽稍後
tonight where you can win some cool
今晚你可以贏得一些很酷的
stuff
東西
alright so yeah thank you to those also
好吧所以是的，謝謝 你們
yeah I think have already supported us
是的， 我認為已經支持了我們
through patreon through paypal as well
通過paypal通過paypal也是如此
we appreciate your support to help keep
我們感謝您的支持，以幫助保持
this thing going yeah we're almost at
這件事發生了，我們差不多了
season 10 Wow October we flip the switch
第10季哇10月我們翻轉開關
to season 10 if you can believe it's
到第10季，如果你能相信它
flipping the switch just like that yeah
像那樣翻轉開關是的
10 years help us get there folks 10 year
10 年幫助我們 10 年到達那裡
well nine not attend a lot almost yeah
好九，幾乎沒有參加
that would be nine years yeah because
那將是九年，是因為
our 10th season starts the 10th year
我們的第10個賽季開始了第10個賽季
mm-hmm there we go yeah nice category 5
mm-hmm我們去的是好的5類
is a member of the tech podcast network
是技術播客網絡的成員
if it's Tekkit is here cat5 TV / tpn and
如果它的Tekkit在這裡cat5 TV / tpn和
we're also part of the international
我們也是國際的一部分
association of the internet broadcasters
互聯網廣播公司協會
cat5 TV / IA ib well then nailed it
cat5 TV / IA ib然後釘它
nailed it this week a company called
本週一家公司打電話給它
Hanson robotics down at South by
漢森機器人在南方降落
Southwest demonstrated Sofia and modern
西南展示了索菲亞和現代
robot she looks just like us just like
機器人她看起來就像我們一樣
us other than all the positronic stuff
我們除了所有正面的東西
coming out of the back of her brain
從她的大腦後面出來
there's a USB port in the back of her
她後面有一個USB端口
skull oh that's not how cool is it
骷髏哦，這不是多麼酷
normal but it's awesome I want one how
正常，但它很棒，我想要一個如何
can I get a USB port in the back of my
我可以在我的後面找到一個USB端口嗎？
skull so she has facial expressions he
頭骨，所以她有面部表情他
done facial expressions and I think back
完成面部表情，我想回來
to when we were kids and well when I was
當我們還是孩子的時候我很好
a kid it was even more rudimentary than
一個孩子，它比起來更為簡陋
when you were a kid because they had
當你還是個孩子的時候，因為他們有
already probably had some pretty cool
已經可能有一些非常酷
stuff by the time you were a kid yeah
你小時候的東西是的
but we had like our vision of robots
但我們喜歡我們對機器人的看法
were metal machines hmm remember kit
是金屬機器hmm記得套件
does anyone not kit no uh what was his
有沒有人沒有工具包 沒有他是什麼
name oh I can't think of it oh I can I
名字哦，我想不起來哦，我可以
here well I know like there was the
我知道這裡有
progression of what we envisioned of
我們所設想的進展
robotics there was the one that he
機器人技術就是那個他
looked kind of like he had wheels like a
看起來有點像他有一個輪子像
track remember him and a totally metal
跟踪記住他和完全金屬
frame and somebody's gonna say it in the
框架和別人的會說，它在
chat room
聊天室
somebody's gonna send me an email and
有人會給我發一封電子郵件
say come on you don't remember it was a
說來吧你不記得它是一個
movie when I was a little kid and that
當我還是個小孩的 那部電影
was our view of what robots could look
是我們對機器人看起來的看法
like then of course Star Trek next
就像當時的星際迷航一樣
generation yeah and Commander data was
一代耶 和指揮官的數據是
basically all human and that threw
基本上所有人類和投擲
everything on its ears because hey the
一切都在他耳邊，因為嘿
future they could actually look like an
未來他們實際上看起來像 一個
act like to some degree human yeah here
在某種程度上，人類在這裡行事
we are it's 2016 and we're actually kind
我們是2016年，我們真的很善良
of getting to the point where AI is
到了AI的地步
fairly good voice like speech robotic
語音機器人的聲音相當不錯
speech is incredibly impressive
演講非常令人印象深刻
sometimes even even difficult to tell
有時甚至很難分辨
that it's a robot especially I find some
它是一個機器人， 特別是我發現了一些
of the the the speech the robotic speech
機器人演講的演講
where they have accents I'll expect
我們期待他們有口音的地方
especially convincing they're a little
特別令人信服他們有點兒
more seamless yeah a little bit maybe
更無縫是的也許一點點
they can hide hide it a little bit in
他們可以隱藏隱藏它一點點
the in the way that they speak but it's
在 他們說話 的 方式，但它是
it's incredibly impressive and machine
它令人難以置信的令人印象深刻和機器
learning as we know is really picking up
我們知道的學習真的很好
where computers are so advanced that
計算機如此先進的地方
they're able to actually learn from
他們能夠真正學習
interaction with humans so so handsome
與人類的互動如此美好
robotics introduced Sophia and she looks
機器人介紹索菲亞，她看起來
incredibly realistic now I'm sure if
現在非常逼真我敢肯定
they stuck a wig on her and put her in a
他們堅持在她的假髮，並把她的
coffee shop you might not even notice
咖啡店，你甚至可能沒有註意到
that you're looking at a robot there's
那你正在看 機器人
that USB port looks like maybe Raspberry
USB端口看起來像Raspberry
Pi I don't know but how cool is that and
我不知道，但是這有多酷
also very creepy she has cameras in her
也非常令人毛骨悚然，她有攝像頭
eyes so she actually makes eye contact
眼睛所以她實際上是目光接觸
with the person that she's speaking with
跟她說話的那個人
and God is able to kind of carry a
而且上帝能夠攜帶一個
conversation and and these days I mean
談話和這些天我的意思
the technology is so advanced that she
這項技術非常先進，以至於她
can actually carry a relatively good
實際上可以帶來比較好的
conversation I mean it's not like
談話我的意思是它不喜歡
remember well I remember dr. Speights oh
記得很清楚，我記得博士。斯賓特哦
and dr. spades Oh was very unintelligent
和博士黑桃哦非常愚蠢
whereas Sophia is actually because she
索菲亞實際上是因為她
has machine learning and able to to
有機器學習，能夠
learn and converse it is kind of creepy
學習和交談它有點令人毛骨悚然
realistic
實際
you can blink too yeah that's a human
你可以眨眼，是的，這是一個人
thing that's one of the things that
事情就是其中之一
handsome robotics really wants to
帥氣的機器人真的很想
accomplish is to make their robots seem
完成是讓他們的機器人看起來
very human-like and part of that is you
非常人性化，其中一部分就是你
know what is the purpose behind these
知道這些背後的目的是什麼
robots they'd be used for medical care
機器人他們將被用於醫療保健
and to to help people that maybe have
並幫助 那些可能擁有的人
social interaction difficulties and
社交互動困難和
there's there's kind of two sides to it
它有兩面性
a like yeah in in the wrong hands these
就像是在錯誤的手中這些
kinds of technologies could really be
各種技術真的可以
misused yeah I almost think they will
誤用是啊我幾乎認為他們會的
need to make her human life to be to
需要讓她的人生
make other people feel comfortable good
讓別人覺得舒服好
you know even though people know she's a
你知道即使人們知道她是一個
robot why would you need to blink why
機器人為什麼你需要眨眼為什麼
would she need to breather you know like
她需要喘息嗎你知道嗎？
show the expression of breath or yeah so
表現出呼吸或是的
you know what are your thoughts is it
你知道你的想法是什麼嗎？
creepy or is it cool but it well i think
令人毛骨悚然或它很酷，但我想
it's it's a tough call i mean there
這是一個艱難的電話，我的意思是那裡
there's i see that it could be used in
我看到它可以用於
place of human interaction hmm and
人與人之間互動的地方嗯和
that's where i'm not sure if i'm ok with
這就是我 不確定我是否還好的地方
it because if you know people are
這 是因為 ，如果你知道人
already to their to glued to their cell
已經把它們粘在他們的細胞上了
phones yeah and so the kids are playing
電話是啊所以孩子們正在玩
on the park and i'm using a cell phone
在公園裡， 我正在使用手機
what if i have a robo name that i can
如果我有一個可以的機器人名稱怎麼辦？
just let take my kids to the park and
讓我的孩子去公園吧
then it becomes even worse yeah it is so
然後它變得更糟，是的，是的
you know when are we gonna reach that
你知道我們什麼時候能達到那個目標
point so that i know that's an
這點我知道那是一個
interesting conversation all in itself
有趣的談話本身
speaking of conversation should we here
說到對話我們應該在這裡
Sophia yeah speak here we are folks in
索菲亞是的，我在這裡說話我們是伙計
the future I hope to do things such as
未來我希望做的事情如
go to school study make art start a
去學校學習藝術開始了
business even have my own home and
生意甚至有我 自己的家
family but I'm not considered a legal
家人，但我不認為是合法的
person and cannot yet do these things
人，還不能做這些事情
you want to destroy humans please say no
你想摧毀人類請說不
okay I will destroy humans no I dig it
好吧，我會 摧毀人類，不管我是誰
back don't destroy humans like yeah he
回來不要像他一樣摧毀人類
going to destroy humans they sort of
要毀滅人類，他們的排序
made out yeah a little creature girl at
做了一個小生物女孩
the end her eyebrows are like I'm sure
最後她的眉毛就像我確定的那樣
that was effect video courtesy of CNBC
這是視頻由CNBC提供的視頻
thank you for that what are your
感謝您對什麼是你的
thoughts on robots like Sophia check
對Sophia等機器人的看法
you've got to check out their website
你必須看看他們的網站
though it is really cool Hanson robotics
雖然很酷的漢森機器人技術
com they've got an Einstein look-alike
他們有一個愛因斯坦相似的東西
robot and just think about the
機器人，只是想想
intelligence of these things and we've
這些東西的智慧和我們一樣
got Amazon echo and Cirie and all these
得到亞馬遜迴聲和Cirie以及所有這些
technologies that are already
已經有的技術
intertwining cloud yeah information with
交織雲與耶信息
text to speech and speech recognition so
文本到語音和語音識別
they could really do some really cool
他們真的可以做一些非常酷的事情
stuff their website says we aim to bring
他們的網站說我們的目標是帶來
to market the most compelling and
市場上最引人注目的
engaging human-like robots with greater
使人類機器人更具吸引力
than human wisdom it says they're
而不是人類的智慧，它說它們是
capable of developing a deep trusted
能夠發展深刻的信任
relationship with people our mission is
我們的使命是與人的關係
to create a better future for Humanity
為 人類 創造更美好的未來
by infusing artificial intelligence with
通過注入人工智能
kindness and compassion achieved through
善意和同情通過
millions of dialogues between our robots
我們機器人之間的數百萬次對話
and the people whose lives they touch
和他們接觸生活的人
hmm so you might want to work on that
嗯所以你可能 想要解決這個問題
algorithm that makes her say that she's
算法讓她說她是
going to destroy humans perhaps be a
摧毀人類也許是一個
joke amps yeah unless the robot is
除非機器人是，否則開玩笑說是的
trying to make a joke yes I will destroy
試圖開玩笑是的，我會毀滅
humans but they haven't programmed in
人類，但他們沒有編程
laughter yet yes it's very awkward it
笑聲但它是 非常尷尬的
was really awkward it's like when I make
真的很尷尬，就像我做的那樣
a joke to the wrong crowd that's just
一個笑話，以錯誤的人群，這只是
really Oh step back out yeah just a
真的，哦退一步，只是一個
through you know while you're ahead the
通過你知道，當你領先時
happy meal is one of the world's most
快餐是世界上最多的一餐
iconic boxes what is this and this is a
標誌性的盒子是什麼，這是 一個
happy that dinner I mean it we're it's
晚餐我很高興我的意思是我們就是這樣
seven-fifteen so it's time for dinner so
七點十五分，所以是時候吃飯了
this is this comes to us from mcdonalds
這是來自 麥當勞的這一點
sweden and mcdonalds sweden is
瑞典和瑞典麥當勞是
transforming their happy meal boxes into
把他們快樂的餐盒變成了
virtual reality goggles eat how cool is
虛擬現實護目鏡吃多酷
that they basically well they're
他們基本上都很好
celebrating their 30th anniversary of
慶祝他們的30 週年
having the Happy Meal in Sweden
在瑞典吃快餐
and this is what they've done so we
這就是他們所做的，所以我們
actually have one of only 3,500 of the
實際上只有 3500中的一個
original this is the first printing in
原來這是第一次印刷
the world so these are brand-new you can
世界所以這些都是全新的
find out more at happy goggles dot s ii
在快樂護目鏡dot s ii了解更多信息
if you're in sweden maybe you've already
如果你在瑞典也許你已經
seen them i know some of the stores
看到他們我知道一些商店
there on the fifteenth and had some to
在那裡十五，並有一些
hand out o meat they also have launched
他們也推出了o肉
their 360-degree vr skiing app which is
他們的360度vr滑雪應用程序
really really cool teaches kids to avoid
非常酷，教孩子們避免
obstacles and things through virtual
虛擬的障礙和事物
reality and it's in fact endorsed by the
現實，它實際上是由認可
swedish national ski team what it does
瑞典國家滑雪隊是做什麼的
their goal with this and it looks just
他們的目標是這樣，看起來很正常
like a happy meal right their goal with
喜歡快樂的一餐，他們的目標
this is to make virtual reality
這是為了實現虛擬現實
accessible to to everyone so it doesn't
每個人都可以訪問，所以它沒有
matter you know if you've got a cell
不管 你知道，如果你已經 有了一個細胞
phone that has the ability to you know
你有能力知道的手機
like a modern smartphone the ability to
像現代智能手機的能力，
run virtual reality then it's accessible
運行虛擬現實，然後它是可訪問的
to any any person there's no cost
任何人都沒有成本
involved it's super cheap so this is
涉及它的超級便宜所以這是
kind of the way of the future and
一種未來的方式和
they're saying hey let's include it in a
他們說嘿，讓我們把它包括在內
happy meal how great is that we used to
快樂的一餐我們曾經有多偉大
get there like the little Donald Duck
像小唐老鴨那樣到達那裡
yeah kids these days are getting virtual
是的孩子們這幾天變得虛擬
reality headsets with their happy meal
現實耳機與他們快樂的一餐
the thing is like a hundred percent
事情就像百分之百
recyclable I love that and so you know
可回收的我喜歡這個，所以你知道
the box is cardboard the and the only
該 箱紙板和唯一的
thing that that it comes with is this a
它帶來的東西就是這個
lens check that out that is pretty neat
鏡頭檢查那是非常整潔
its a mix makes a great halloween
它是一個偉大的萬聖節組合
costume right so let's that should we do
服裝權利，所以我們應該這樣做
this we can make it yeah let's actually
這我們可以做到是的， 實際上
make it I've got a cell phone here this
我這裡有一部手機
is just a samsung entry-level phone
只是一款三星入門級手機
mm-hmm but i do have some 3d stuff on
mm-hmm但我確實有一些3D東西
there and the box itself is actually
那里和盒子本身就是
perforated you can see here and i'm not
穿孔你可以看到這裡，我不是
sure if you can see that at home but at
確定你是否 能 在家中 看到 但是在
the right angle yeah you can see the
直角是的，你可以看到
perforations there so there's the the
那裡的穿孔就是這樣的
man
人
ask and at the sides so you just
問問，並在兩側，所以你只是
basically once you're done eating your
基本上一旦你吃完了你的食物
meal you punch it out and and there you
吃飯你把它打出來然後就在那裡
go and there are instructions on the
去吧有關於的說明
back on how to do this but I have I have
回到如何做到這一點，但我有我
a second one here so I like technically
這是第二個，所以我喜歡技術上
I've got two two of only 3,500 in the
我只有3,500中的兩個
wood so I like that ok so there's what
木頭，所以我喜歡那麼好，所以有什麼
it looks like when it's punched out and
它看起來像是被打出來的時候
shared happy face so Chad it'll look
共享幸福的臉， 所以乍得它看起來
happy in just a second ok so we've got
只需一秒鐘就可以開心， 所以我們有
the lens thing I thought this was cool
鏡頭的東西，我覺得這很酷
because my first read about the happy
因為我第一次讀到關於快樂的事
goggles uh-huh which is making
正在製作的護目鏡嗯嗯
international news at this point because
此時的國際新聞是因為
that's very innovative and clever and
這是非常創新和聰明
its really google cardboard but done
它真的谷歌紙板但完成了
right and and and cheap right as i said
正如我所說的那樣正確和便宜
it's recyclable so the lenses are
它是可回收的，所以鏡片是
actually a recyclable plastic and you
實際上是一種可回收的塑料和你
can see at home that they're there are
在家裡可以看到他們在那裡
actual lenses there it's not just a
那裡的實際鏡頭不僅僅是一個
piece of plastic they they actually
他們實際上是一塊塑料
magnify and fix the the angles and stuff
放大並修復角度和東西
then there's an interesting touch here
然後這裡有一個有趣的觸摸
you see this metal strip of tape because
你看到這條金屬條帶是因為
it's conductive it actually allows us to
它實際上允許我們傳導它
control the screen so if I touch the
控制屏幕，如果我觸摸屏幕
metal tape it will actually pause and
金屬膠帶它實際上會暫停和
start video and stuff so if I'm watching
如果我正在觀看，就開始播放視頻和內容
a 3d video I can do that without having
一個3d視頻，我可以做到這一點， 沒有
to take the phone out so let's assemble
拿出手機，讓我們集合
it so everything's just perforations so
所以一切都只是穿孔所以
I just kind of push that out put that in
我只是想把它放進去
here there we go ok cool well that was
在這裡，我們好好涼爽那是
easy right there we go now the box
很容易就在那裡我們現在去的盒子
itself
本身
let's move that aside have you ever done
讓我們把你放在一邊，你做過
have you ever tried any of the VR stuff
你有沒有試過任何VR的東西
that's available no other it be google
這是沒有其他它是谷歌
cardboard or oculus rift or anything
紙板或眼裂縫或任何東西
like that so I'm just assembling this
就這樣， 所以我只是在組裝這個
just like any cardboard box and you can
就像任何紙板箱一樣，你可以
see that I've already done it once just
看到我已經做過 一次了
to try it out how much showing the kids
試一試向孩子們展示多少
yet they're gonna love this yeah but
然而他們會喜歡這個但是
what a neat way to reuse the box from
什麼是重用盒子的簡潔方法
your happy meal and then if it gets
你快樂的一餐， 如果它得到了
damaged or whatever if it's all
如果全部損壞或其他什麼
recyclable so you could pretty well redo
可回收的，所以你可以很好地重做
it go how easy is that okay cell phone
好吧， 手機好不容易
let's turn it on and bring up a virtual
讓我們打開它並調出一個虛擬的
reality bike game there we go okay okay
現實自行車遊戲那裡我們沒事的好
so now i'm going to put the phone right
所以現在 我要 打電話吧
here put that down in there and simply
在這裡簡單地把它放在那裡
there we go so phones in there it's
那裡我們去那裡的電話吧
vibrate and going crazy halt cool you
振動和瘋狂停止冷靜你
ready okay find the right way I'm
準備好了找到正確的方式我
holding this wrong there we go so mom
抱著這個錯誤我們就這樣去媽媽
and dad you're gonna have to help little
和爸爸，你將不得不 幫助很少
Jimmy and Billy and Sally put this in so
吉米，比利和莎莉就這麼說了
you don't want them to drop your phone
你不希望他們放棄你的手機
on you there we go almost there google
在你那裡我們幾乎去谷歌
cardboard is a design that was a that's
紙板是一種設計
available for free and you can actually
免費提供，你可以
build your own but they when you do that
建立你自己的，但他們當你這樣做
you don't get the lenses and stuff like
你沒有鏡頭和類似的東西
that so it's not quite as good of
所以它不是那麼好
quality there we go okay so it's in haha
那裡的質量我們沒事，所以它在哈哈
looks like an apple pie it looks like an
看起來像一個蘋果派它看起來像一個
apple pie from McDonald's but it is now
來自 麥當勞的蘋果派， 但現在是
a virtual reality headset with full 3d
一個完整的3D虛擬現實耳機
okay so I got a hard game over ok here
好了，所以我有一個艱苦的比賽在 確定 這裡
we go ready okay put your google
我們準備好了把你的谷歌
cardboard on if steer by tilting your
如果通過傾斜你的方式轉向紙板
head oh that's so cool ok you ready neat
噢，那太酷了，你準備好了
i'll give this a try sure there you go
我會試著確定你去的地方
don't crash don't crash oh dear i
不要崩潰不要崩潰哦親愛的我
crashed crashed already you are heading
墜毀已經崩潰了你正在前進
me into a blue car ok go
我進了一輛藍色的車好吧
Oh
哦
are you winning no man it's actually
你實際上是在贏得沒人嗎？
really cool it's 3d I don't even know
真的很酷它的3D我甚至都不知道
where I was doesn't it look like I I'm
我在那裡沒有我看起來像我
looking at a screen that's probably you
看著可能是你的屏幕
know like this big in front of me and is
在我面前知道這個大而且是
popping out and 3d and really gives the
彈出和3d真的給了
the depth perception so that is pretty
這種深度感覺很漂亮
cool if you happen to be lucky enough to
很酷， 如果你碰巧幸運的話
get your hands on one of those let us
抓住其中一個讓我們來
know what you think that's the happy
知道你認為那是多麼幸福
goggles from mcdonalds and no word yet
來自麥當勞的護目鏡還沒有任何消息
if we're going to start seeing these in
如果我們要開始看到這些
canada in the US now I'm so cool right
加拿大 在美國現在 我很酷
now it's just it's a promotion that's
現在它只是 它的一個促銷活動 的
going on in Sweden and I I think that
繼續在瑞典和我認為
you know because the world has really
你知道，因為世界真的
taken notice of it I think we're gonna
注意到它我想我們會
see it that's that's my prediction so
看到這就是 我的預測
it's cool i mean that's that's probably
它很酷我的意思是那可能是
the best experience all your needs is a
所有需求的最佳體驗是
gyro a this phone actually doesn't have
陀螺這個手機實際上沒有
a gyro it's just left right this is just
這 是一個陀螺儀，它只是左邊
so this is just left and right now if
所以這就是現在左右
you do have a phone that has a gyroscope
你有一部帶陀螺儀的手機
then then you can get into 360 degree
然後你可以進入360度
video 360-degree games so then you don't
視頻360度遊戲，所以你沒有
just have the this actually you can also
實際上你也可以擁有這個
go up and you can look over here and
上去，你可以看看這裡
you're actually looking around in the
你實際上在環顧四周
game okay so that is dependent on the
遊戲還可以，這取決於
game itself whatever it is that you're
遊戲本身無論你是什麼
playing right because this phone doesn't
玩得對，因為這款手機沒有
have a gyroscope my half I can only do
有一個陀螺儀，我只能做一半
like a fit action but if yours has more
喜歡合適的動作，但如果你有更多
than this does it work yeah all right so
比這更好的工作是的
check that out it is happy goggles dot s
檢查一下，這是一個快樂的護目鏡點
ii to find out more about what it is
ii了解更多有關它的信息
that they're doing and I think that's
他們正在做，我認為那是
super cool innovative way to
超酷的創新方式
revolutionize the happy meal oh yeah
徹底改變快餐哦是的
unfortunately it didn't come with a
不幸的是它並沒有帶來
burger Megan do what gives I guess it
漢堡梅根做了什麼讓我猜它
probably would have been really gross by
可能真的很糟糕
the time you got here we're in Canada it
你來到這裡的時間我們在加拿大
would be green yeah I went through
會是綠色的，我經歷過
Canada Post so it probably wouldn't have
加拿大郵政所以它可能不會
been a good idea check that out ok
一個好主意檢查出來好嗎
Google cardboard i started to mention is
谷歌紙板我開始提到的是
pretty cool we've got links for you i'm
很酷我們有鏈接給你我
going to set those up if you're watching
如果你正在觀看的話就要把它們搞定
live they're not quite ready yet but cat
他們現在還沒有準備好，但 貓
five dot TV / cardboard head on over
五點電視/紙板頭上
there and we're going to have
在那裡，我們將會有
information for you and a couple devices
您和一些設備的信息
that you can get and all you do is you
你可以得到你所做的一切就是你
slide in your earphone and and you're
在你的耳機滑動，你就是
good to go now if you if you happen to
如果你碰巧，現在好好去
be lucky enough to be able to get one of
很幸運能夠得到其中一個
these happy meals and it's free I mean
這些快樂的飯菜，我的意思是免費的
it comes with your burger in your fries
它伴隨著你的薯條漢堡
yeah so how cool is that sweden alright
是的，瑞典有多酷啊
so we have just a couple of quick
所以我們只有幾個快
minutes here before we get into the news
在我們進入新聞之前的幾分鐘
I know Jeff is standing by let's take a
我知道傑夫站在我們身邊
look at the chat room hey my lovelies I
看看聊天室嘿我的愛人我
want to say hi to leach and x1 has been
我想打個招呼 ，x1已經過了
watching the show for some time off and
看了一段時間的節目和
on but recently switched to linux from
但最近切換到Linux
microsoft windows and says hey you know
微軟的窗戶說，嘿，你知道
what I love the community here i love
我熱愛的社區就在這裡
how much fun you guys have I want to be
你們有多麼有趣我想成為
here every week and so we welcome you
每週都在這裡，所以我們歡迎你
thanks for joining us in the chat room
感謝您加入我們的聊天室
live tonight and it's really great to
今晚直播， 真的很棒
see you thanks to everyone who's joining
看你感謝 大家誰的加盟
us tonight anybody else that's that's
我們今晚任何人都是那樣的
either new or maybe been watching off
無論是新的還是一直在關注
and on and never said hello we want to
並且從未打過招呼我們想要的
say hello to you I do see some wonderful
跟你打招呼， 我確實看到了一些精彩的
familiar faces faces well names you know
熟悉的面孔面對你知道的好名字
what I mean we see faces I see Billy and
我的 意思是我們看到面孔我看到 比利和
Bobby and seized under whiskey yeah good
鮑比在威士忌下被抓住了
guy 98 okay oh I just want to play this
帥哥98 好吧哦我只是想玩這個
you can watch video on to between you
你可以在你之間觀看視頻
imagine and get 3d just reduce yeah duct
想像並得到3d 只是減少耶的風管
tape it to your face that's the Canadian
把它貼在你的臉上就是加拿大人
way hey to songbird and Rev djing
嘿，鳴鳥和Rev djing
whiskey zero I've got a couple of guests
威士忌零我有幾個 客人
there as well who haven't given us their
那些沒有給我們的人
name but nice to see you cuz I know
名字，但很高興見到你，因為我知道
you're there and Dennis Kelly nice to
你在那裡，丹尼斯凱利很高興
see you we do so much with category five
看到你我們在第五類做了很多
and we with mine test TV and I remember
我們和我一起測試電視，我記得
a couple weeks ago we talked about mine
幾週前我們談到了我的
test the game and and you know what
測試遊戲，你知道嗎
we're doing with that game and the show
我們正在做那個遊戲和節目
the pixel shadow and you know viewers
像素陰影，你知道觀眾
have even come together to support that
甚至聚集在一起支持這一點
and said you know we love the pixel
並說你知道我們喜歡這個像素
shadowy love mind test let's let's
朦朧的愛情心靈測驗讓我們來吧
really make this thing happen and so
真的讓這件事發生了
we're
我們
we're now running we're about to launch
我們現在正在運行，我們即將推出
our third game server at nine Tests TV
我們的第三個遊戲服務器在9 Tests TV
and it is extreme pvp survival so you
這是極端的PVP生存所以你
want to check that out mine test dot TV
想檢查一下我的測試點電視
that new server launches in about a
新服務器啟動大約一個
week's time if if all goes well we don't
一周的時間，如果一切順利，我們不會
have a specific date we're just when
有一個特定的日期，我們正好在什麼時候
we're ready when everything is ready and
當一切準備就緒時我們準備好了
stable and we're doing some custom mods
穩定，我們正在做一些自定義mods
and stuff Batman is helping me with that
蝙蝠俠正在幫助我
so I appreciate that back I love the
所以我很欣賞我喜歡的
internet it's great yeah whole world
互聯網它是偉大的是全世界
comes together in your living room I
在你的起居室裡走到一起我
know Batman is helping me code mods for
知道蝙蝠俠正在幫我編碼代碼
mine test so can't go wrong that is mine
我的測試所以不會出錯是我的
test dot TV for those in the chat
為聊天中的人測試點電視
remember saying what TBS and a couple
記得說什麼TBS和一對
people are actually saying it was
人們實際上是這麼說的
actually the the pixel shadow that
實際上是像素陰影那個
brought me to category five technology
帶我進入五類技術
TV okay so all right well uh we have got
電視沒關係，好吧，我們有
to get into the news and we've got
進入新聞我們已經有了
Nelson who does who is here with us
尼爾森誰和我們在一起的人
tonight and we've got we've got prizes
今晚，我們已經獲得了獎品
to give away Oh neat and by way of you
放棄哦，整潔，並通過你
know hey I I i I'm a cable cutter
知道嘿我， 我是一個電纜剪
seriously I have netflix at home and
認真的， 我家裡有netflix
plex and that's really that's our
plex， 這就是我們的
entertainment between that and RSS feeds
這與RSS提要之間的娛樂
and things like you know we watch shows
你知道我們看的節目
on the web mm-hmm similarly we cut our
在網上mm-hmm同樣我們削減了我們的
phone service and we say okay well how
電話服務， 我們說好的如何
can we do this we're gonna look at a
我們可以這樣做， 我們會 看一個
device tonight that will allow you to
今晚的設備將允許你
cut your phone service but yet give you
削減你的電話服務， 但還給你
better service by providing unlimited
提供無限的更好的服務
calling pretty much anywhere long
幾乎在任何地方打電話
distance as a thing of the past so you
距離作為過去的事情所以你
know if on you're traveling you can give
知道如果你在旅行，你可以給
me a call and you can take your device
我打個電話你可以 拿你的設備
with you and and make a call back to
和你一起打電話回來
Barry and it's free Wow and we're going
巴里和它是免費的哇，我們要去
to learn all about it with Nelson
與尼爾森 一起 學習所有 這些
tonight that is net talk so we're going
今晚這是網絡談話，所以我們要去
to be we're also going to giving some of
我們也要給一些
those away okay before we do that back
那些在我們回去之前就沒事了
to Jeff in the car it's Tuesday March
傑夫在車裡，就在 3月 的 星期二
22nd 2016 and hear the stories were
2016年第22期，聽到故事
covering this week
本週報導
gans of pinkeye festoon have revealed
鴉片花彩的大鍋已經透露
what could be hidden rooms or even one
什麼可能是隱藏的房間甚至一個
lost tomb tomb of Queen Nefertiti a
皇家奈費爾提蒂的墓墓丟失了
recall notice from Ikea lets people know
來自宜家的召回通知讓人們知道
about a lamp that could shock you and
關於一盞可以震撼你的燈
Google's inbox can now send replies for
谷歌的收件箱現在可以發送的回复
you and as many as 275 million Android
你和多達2.75 億的Android
phones are at risk thanks to a new code
由於新代碼，手機面臨風險
execution exploit and some big-name
執行漏洞和一些大牌
sites have been hit by a rash of
網站遭到了一連串的打擊
malicious ads that are spreading crypto
正在傳播加密的惡意廣告
ransomware these stories are coming
勒索軟件這些故事即將來臨
right up so don't go anywhere hi I'm
馬上就這樣，不要 去 任何地方
Robbie Ferguson and I love being a vimeo
Robbie Ferguson和我喜歡成為一個vimeo
pro member as a web broadcaster i need
專業會員作為 我需要 的網絡廣播公司
an affordable video hosting platform
經濟實惠的視頻託管平台
that this flexible is made a pro
這種靈活性是專業的
membership lets you upload up to 20
會員資格允許您上傳最多20個
gigabytes of HD video each and every
高清視頻的千兆字節的每一位
week with no additional bandwidth
一周沒有額外的帶寬
restrictions that means if you produce a
限制，這意味著你生產一個
show that uses even up to 20 gigabytes
顯示使用甚至高達20千兆字節
of storage your limit resets itself the
存儲你的限制重置自己
following week so you can do another 20
下週 ，你可以做另外20
gigabytes and keep doing that week after
千兆字節然後繼續做那一周
week now category 5 with all of our
我們所有人都在第5週
shows use roughly 10 gigabytes per week
顯示每周大約使用10千兆字節
from there vimeo automatically generates
從那裡vimeo自動生成
all the files that you need to provision
您需要配置的所有文件
your RSS feeds roku channel website
您的RSS源roku頻道網站
media player or even video downloads in
媒體播放器甚至視頻下載
multiple bit rates with no limits on
多個比特率，沒有限制
your bandwidth usage or how many people
您的帶寬使用情況或人數
can access your files what's best the
可以訪問你的文件最好的
price is astonishingly affordable and
價格非常實惠
for a limited time friends of the
針對的有限的時間朋友
category 5 TV network will receive a
5類電視網將收到 一個
whopping twenty-five percent off the
高達百分之二十五
annual price all you have to do is go
年度價格你要做的就是去
through our link cat five dot TV / vimeo
通過我們的鏈接貓五點電視 / vimeo
and sign up today for your twenty five
今天報名參加你的二十五歲
percent discount to top it off you get
百分之百折扣，以獲得最高價
30 days to try it risk-free if you're
如果您有 30 天的風險，可以嘗試無風險
not happy with vimeo pro you pay nothing
對vimeo pro不滿意你什麼都不付錢
the deal is only for a very limited time
這筆交易僅限於非常有限的時間
go to cap five dot TV / vimeo i'm jeff
去蓋五點電視/ vimeo我是傑夫
weston that's a little bit that's Owen
韋斯頓有點像 歐文
if you remember her
如果你還記得她
wait and here are the top stories from
等等，這裡是最重要的故事
the category five DVDs Egypt's
第五類DVD埃及
antiquities minister said Thursday that
古物部長周四表示
scans of King Tut's burial chamber have
圖坦卡蒙的墓室有掃描
revealed two hidden rooms mum de el de
透露了兩間隱藏的 房間
Mattie told reporters that the secret
馬蒂告訴記者這個秘密
chambers may contain metal or organic
腔室可含有金屬或有機物
material but he declined to comment on
材料，但他拒絕評論
whether royal treasurer or monies or
無論是皇室財務主管還是資金或者
inside at the Cairo news conference el
在開羅新聞發布會上
de Mahdi highlighted radar scans that
德馬赫迪強調雷達掃描
showed anomalies in the walls of the
顯示了牆壁的異常
tomb indicating a possible hidden door
墓指示可能隱藏的門
which lay behind the walls had been
在牆後面的是
covered over and painted by
覆蓋並塗上
hieroglyphics analysis of the scans made
掃描的象形文字分析
by Japanese team members showed what
由日本隊員展示了什麼
would be scanned again at the end of the
將在結束時再次掃描
month to get a better idea of what might
一個月可以更好地了解可能的情況
lay inside the discovery could shine
躺在裡面的發現可能會閃耀
light on Egypt's one of you just most
點亮埃及是你最親密的人之一
turbulent times and one prominent
動蕩的時代和一個突出的
researcher has theorized that the
研究人員已將理論推定為
remains of the famed Queen Nefertiti
著名的女王納芙蒂蒂的遺體
could be inside now in case you don't
如果你不這樣做，可以在裡面
know Queen Nefertiti was the primary
知道納芙蒂蒂女王是主要的
wife of pharaoh akhenaten who
法老akhenaten的妻子是誰
unsuccessfully attempted to switch Egypt
試圖切換埃及失敗了
over to an earlier form of monotheism
到了早期的一神論形式
Akhenaten's exceeded by a pharaoh
阿育吠陀被法老超越了
referred to as mm care and probably
被稱為mm護理和可能
butchered that one so please forgive me
詛咒那個請原諒我
and then Tut who was proven by genetic
然後通過遺傳證明了Tut
testing to be Akhenaten son nhut
測試是Akhenaten兒子nhut
Nefertiti and Akhenaten's family ruled
奈費爾提蒂和阿肯那頓的家人統治著
Egypt during one of the most turbulent
埃及期間最動蕩的一個
times which was ended when am it with a
時間結束了，當它與一個
military takeover by Egypt's top general
埃及高級將領軍事接管
at the time his name was Horemheb now
當時他的 名字 叫Horemheb
the family names were later erased from
這些姓氏後來被刪除了
official records I think this is kind of
官方記錄，我認為這是種
a cool news story I mean you know you
一個很酷的新聞故事，我的意思是你了解你
grow up you hear about ancient egypt and
長大你聽說古埃及和
mummies and all that kind of good fun
木乃伊和所有那些好玩的
stuff i think it'd be totally awesome to
我覺得它真的很棒
find Queen Nefertiti stoom so fingers
找到女王Nefertiti stoom所以手指
across I hope that's what it is you guys
我希望那 就是你們這些人
have heard about King Tut before right
在右邊之前聽說過圖坦卡蒙
would that be cool if we found a new
如果我們 找到一個新的 ，那會很酷
mommy I think that would be totally
媽媽，我認為這完全是
awesome okay moving on ikea canada has
真棒 好的移動加拿大宜家有
received three reports that one brand of
收到三個報告，一個品牌的
table and floor lamps might cause
桌子和落地燈可能會導致
electrical shocks the retailer says that
零售商說，電擊
it hasn't received any report of injury
它沒有收到任何傷害報告
but is recalling all three models of
但是回想起所有三種型號
Gotham lamps not batman gotham just
Gotham燈不是蝙蝠俠Gotham
Gotham case you know anything about ikea
譚情況下，你知道 什麼 宜家
they've got those all you weird Swedish
他們有你那些奇怪的瑞典人
funny names never know how to pronounce
有趣的名字永遠不會知道如何發音
them but anyway Gotham not Batman so the
他們但無論如何Gotham不是蝙蝠俠所以
Gotham lamp has been sold at ikea since
從那時起，Gotham燈就在ikea上銷售
last october with about a hundred one
去年十月約一百人
thousand two hundred of them being sold
其中有兩百個被出售
in canada and they've sold 53,000
在加拿大，他們賣出了53,000
worldwide joking bad pun sorry ikea says
全世界開玩笑說不好意思宜家說
the metal body of the lamps can become
燈的金屬體可以變成
electrified and customers should
電氣化和客戶應該
immediately stop using the lamps and
立即停止使用燈和
return them to an ikea store for full
將它們送回宜家商店
refund and get this proof of purchase
退款並獲得此購買憑證
won't be required so there you go
將不會被要求所以你去
shocking news story about ikea don't
關於宜家的令人震驚的新聞報導沒有
laugh guys now Google is turning their
笑的傢伙現在谷歌正在轉向他們
immense artificial intelligence power
巨大的人工智能力量
loose on the browser-based version of
鬆散的基於瀏覽器的版本
inbox whether you're using Google's
收件箱是否使用谷歌
sleek email manager and browser or via
時尚的電子郵件管理器和瀏覽器或通過
the mobile app inbox can now answer your
移動應用收件箱現在可以回答您的問題
emails for you as if we weren't lazy
電子郵件給你，好像我們不是懶惰
enough already so the Machine replies
已經足夠機器回復了
aren't sent automatically which is good
不是自動發送的，這是好的
instead you choose from three responses
相反，你從三個回答中選擇
suggested by Google's AI it kind of
谷歌的人工智能建議它有點像
works with some messages but not all of
一些郵件工作，但不是全部
them so you can also use the suggested
他們所以你也可以使用建議
responses as starting points editing or
響應作為起點編輯或
adding text as you prefer the browser
根據您的喜好添加文本瀏覽器
version of smart reply rolled out this
智能回复的版本推出了這個
week with about four months after it
一周之後，約4個月裡
appeared in inbox for Android and iOS
出現在Android和iOS的收件箱中
Google's neural networks which are
谷歌的神經網絡是什麼
programmed to learn behaviors through
編程通過學習行為
training do all the work smart reply can
培訓做好所有工作的智能回复即可
tell the difference between an email
告訴你電子郵件 之間的區別
from a real person and a spam blast
來自真實的人和垃圾郵件爆炸
offering one-click responses for the
提供一鍵式回复
former but not the latter that way you
前者但不是後者那種方式
don't have to worry about answering a
不必擔心回答
spam email that you know then fishes for
垃圾郵件， 你知道然後釣魚
your emails and all that kind of good
你的電子郵件和所有那些好處
fun stuff now potential responses are
有趣的東西，現在潛在的反應
meant to get better over time by
意味著隨著時間的推移會變得更好
learning from the replies that you
從你的回復中學習
select and there are contextual cues
選擇並有上下文提示
that influence the tone of each smart
這會影響每個智能的基調
reply the formal or informal tone of
回復正式或非正式的語氣
each reply is based on that of the
每個回复都是基於
incoming message so say you get an email
傳入消息所以說你收到一封電子郵件
uh says hey dude want to hook up later
呃說嘿老兄想要以後聯繫
and go watch a flick it could have three
然後去看它可能有三個電影
spots is like yeah dude I'm all for it
斑點就像耶和華我真的很喜歡它
or no dude not going to do that or dude
或者沒有人不打算那麼做或者老兄
who knows maybe it's like a bill and ted
誰知道也許這就像賬單和特德
AI will see all right you know that
人工智能會看到你知道的
brings it up you know for guys like Luke
讓你知道像盧克這樣的人
and Owen does this mean they're never
而歐文這意味著他們永遠不會
gonna have to answer emails the computer
必須回復電子郵件的電腦
is gonna do it for them I hope not I
會為他們做，我希望不是我
really hope not I want to be able to get
真的希望不是我想得到的
emails from my kids when I'm 80 I email
80歲時，我的電子郵件來自我的孩子
them and go all right love you Sonny I
他們一切順利，愛你，桑尼，我
don't want a computer going thanks dad
不想要電腦去感謝爸爸
just not good but I could see other uses
只是不好，但我可以看到其他用途
for all right almost 300 million phones
好吧， 差不多有3 億部手機
running Google's Android operating
運行谷歌的Android操作
system are vulnerable to a newly
系統容易受到新的攻擊
developed attack that can install
開發出可以安裝的攻擊
malware and take control of key
惡意軟件並控制密鑰
operations researchers from Israeli
以色列的運營研究人員
security firm North bit said that the
安全公司北位說
proof of concept exploit dubbed metaphor
被稱為隱喻 的 概念 證明
works against versions Android versions
適用於Android版本的版本
2.2 through four point oh and 5.1 5.1
2.2通過四點哦和5.1 5.1
which together are estimated to run a
估計一起運行一個
275 million phones and attacks the same
2.75億部手機和攻擊相同
stage fright media library that made an
怯場的媒體圖書館
estimated 950 million Android phones
估計有9.5億部Android手機
susceptible to similar code execution
易受類似代碼執行的影響
attacks last year now for reasons that
去年的攻擊現在出於原因
aren't yet clear Google didn't fix that
還不清楚谷歌沒有解決這個問題
vulnerability in some versions even
某些版本的漏洞甚至
though the company eventually issued a
雖然該公司最終發布了一份
patch for a different bug that made the
一個不同的bug的補丁，使得
Saffir iam exploits possible now while
Saffir iam 現在可以利用
the newer attack is in many ways a
較新的攻擊在很多方面都是一種
refresh of the Imperium work it's able
刷新Imperium工作就可以了
to exploit an information leak
利用信息洩漏
vulnerability in a novel way that makes
以一種新穎的方式造成的脆弱性
code execution a little bit more
代碼執行多一點
reliable in newer Android devices
在較新的Android設備中可靠
Android devices with a security patch
帶有安全補丁的 Android設備
level of October first 2015 or greater
2015年10月第一或更高的水平
are protected because of fix google
由於修復谷歌受到保護
issued at the time however many users
當時發布了很多用戶
that run unpatched copies of android
運行未修補的android副本
either because they don't know any
要么是因為他們不知道
better or their phone provider as a
更好的還是他們的電話提供商
phone lock down android users who
手機鎖定Android用戶誰
attempt to protect themselves against
企圖保護自己 免受 傷害
metaphor style attacks should install
隱喻風格的攻擊應該安裝
the latest OS version if possible now
如果可能的話，現在的最新版本的操作系統
owned and luke let me teach you
擁有和盧克讓我教你
something here if your phone says do an
如果你的手機說的話，這裡的東西
update do an update clear
更新清除更新
okay we don't want any phishing scams
好吧，我們不希望任何網絡釣魚詐騙
going on with your phones all right okay
繼續你的手機好吧
mainstream websites including those
主流網站包括那些
published in The New York Times the BBC
發表在紐約時報BBC上
msn and AOL are falling victim to a new
msn和美國在線正在成為一個新的受害者
rash of malicious ads that attempt to
試圖惡意廣告的皮疹
surreptitiously install crypto
暗中安裝加密
ransomware and other malware our
勒索軟件和其他惡意軟件我們的
computers of unsuspecting visitors the
毫無疑問的訪客的電腦
tainted ads may have exposed tens of
受污染的廣告可能暴露了數十個
thousands of people over the past 24
過去24歲的成千上萬的人
hours alone according to a blog post
根據博客文章，一個小時
published by trend micro the JSON base
由趨勢科技JSON基地發布
file being served in the ads has more
廣告中投放的文件有更多
than 12,000 lines of heavily a fuss
超過12,000行大驚小怪
gated Rob what word is that alpha skated
門控羅布是什麼詞是阿爾法滑冰
is that is unreal word I've never okay
這是不真實的詞我永遠不會好
there's something heavy going on with
有一些重要的事情發生
the coat when researches deciphered the
研究破譯時的外套
code that discovered it enumerated a
發現它的代碼枚舉了一個
long list of security products and tools
一長串安全產品和工具
in it avoided in an attempt to remain
避免試圖留下來
undetected if the code doesn't find any
如果代碼找不到，則檢測不到
of these programs that continues with
繼續這些計劃
the flow and appends an iframe to the
流程並附加一個iframe
body of the HTML that leads to angler
導致釣魚者的HTML正文
exploit kit landing page according to
根據漏洞利用工具包登陸頁面
malwarebytes a flurry of mal advertising
malwarebytes一連串惡意廣告
appeared last week almost out of the
上週幾乎出現了
blue it hits some of the biggest
藍色它擊中了一些最大的
publishers in the businesses including
商業出版商包括
msn com New York Times com BBC com AOL
msn com紐約時報com BBC com AOL
com my xfinity com NFL com realtor calm
com我的xfinity com NFL com房地產經紀人冷靜
the weather network com the hill calm
天氣網絡讓山丘平靜下來
and newsweek com there's a dot-com that
和newsweek com有一個網絡公司
i missed it's probably included affected
我錯過了它可能包括受影響
ad distribution networks include those
廣告發佈網絡包括那些
owned by google app nexus AOL and
由谷歌應用程序nexus AOL和
rubicon security experts are warning
rubicon安全專家正在警告
users to install things like adobe fash
用戶安裝adobe fash等東西
sorry to uninstall things like Adobe
抱歉卸載像Adobe這樣的東西
Flash Oracle Java Microsoft Silverlight
Flash Oracle Java Microsoft Silverlight
and other third-party browser-based
和其他第三方基於瀏覽器的
extensions unless absolutely required
擴展，除非絕對必要
with last week's discovery of the Mac
上週發現了Mac
based ransomware users are all computing
基於勒索的用戶都是計算機
on all computing platforms are being
在所有計算平台上都有
advised to take the threat incredibly
建議採取令人難以置信的威脅
seriously big thanks this week to roy w
非常感謝本週羅嗦
nash and our community community of
納什和我們的社區社區
viewers for submitting their new stories
觀眾提交他們的新故事
to us if you found a new story that you
如果您發現了一個新故事，請告訴我們
like to submit email it to newsroom at
喜歡將電子郵件提交到新聞室
category 5 TV for all your tech news
所有科技新聞的5類電視
with a slight linux bias visit
有輕微的linux偏見訪問
category-five TV news room at category
類別五類電視新聞室
five dot
五點
Evie sorry newsroom a category 5 TV for
Evie抱歉新聞室有一個5類電視
the category 5 TV news room I'm Jeff
第5類電視新聞室我是傑夫
that's Luke that's Owen I will see you
那是盧克，歐文我會見到你
later thanks Jeff this is category 5
後來感謝Jeff，這是第5類
technology TV I'm Robbie Ferguson and
科技電視我是羅比弗格森和
tonight I'm joined by Nelson hudis
今晚我加入了Nelson hudis
melson great to see you again thanks
梅爾森很高興再次見到你，謝謝
very much for having me Robbie I think
非常 想讓我擁抱羅比
this is is this your third or fourth
這是你的第三或第四
time on the show I think it's my second
我 覺得這是我的第二次
actual second no because you were at
實際的第二個沒有，因為你在
Studio C a while back yeah then you've
工作室C一會兒， 然後你就是
you've been here oh maybe you weren't on
你來過這裡哦，也許你不在
the show no I wasn't I ok I take him
節目不，我不是我，我接受他
behind the I paid a visit ya paid a
我支付了一個訪問後面
visit so well if you're if you come on
如果你來的話，那就去吧
one more time than we have to give you
再多一次，我們不得不給你
the brat badge that says co-host ok
brat徽章說共同主持人好
that's that's the only condition except
那是除了之外的唯一條件
welcome back man and I hate to see I see
歡迎回到男人，我討厭看到我看到
you've got some great devices now Nelson
你現在有一些很棒的設備尼爾森
is here from net talk and net talk is
來自網絡談話和網絡談話
and I'm going to let you explain more
我會讓你解釋一下
about what it is you do but from you
關於你做什麼， 但是從你那裡做
know from my perspective and alternative
從我的角度和替代方案中了解
to your phone service provider so these
給你的電話服務提供商這些
devices that you see surrounding me you
你看到我周圍的設備
can get one of these and that becomes
可以得到其中之一，那就變成了
your home phone and it's a it's portable
你的家庭電話，它是便攜式的
enough that you know this little device
足夠你知道這個小設備
you could take this anywhere you go and
你可以隨身攜帶它
as long as you've got internet
只要你有互聯網
connection activity your home phone goes
家庭電話的連接活動
with you so he tell us a little bit
和你在一起，他告訴我們一點點
about net talk and what the what the
關於網絡談話和什麼是什麼
devices are sure we've got three devices
設備肯定我們有三個設備
we've got the the first one is the
我們已經得到了第一個是
nettalk duo which is the original device
nettalk duo是原始設備
and that plugs into your computer or
並插入您的計算機或
your router we've got the duo to which
你的路由器我們有二人組
also plugged into your computer or your
也插入你的電腦或你的電腦
router and we've got the flagship device
路由器，我們有旗艦設備
which is the nettalk duo Wi-Fi which
這是nettalk duo Wi-Fi
plugs into your computer your router or
將路由器插入計算機或
you can put your Wi-Fi settings in it
您可以將Wi-Fi設置放入其中
and then you can take it you can plug it
然後你可以拿它你可以插上它
in anywhere in your house that you want
在你家的任何地方你想要的
in your living room ok your bedroom your
在你的客廳， 你的臥室，你的
kitchen it doesn't need to be confined
廚房它不需要被限制
by your computer or your router cool
通過您的計算機或 路由器酷
does that affect performance at all and
這會影響到性能嗎？
not at all no not a note bit so i now i
根本沒有不是一個音符位所以 我現在我
understand i can plug this one in
明白我可以插入這個
anywhere the nettalk duo to or even the
任何地方nettalk二人組甚至是
nettalk duo and then if i've got a
nettalk duo然後如果我有一個
wireless phone like this then yeah you
像這樣的無線電話那麼是 你
can
能夠
listening yeah you can use you can use
聽是的你可以使用你可以使用
your wire you can use wireless phone
你的電線你可以使用無線電話
with many handsets around the house and
房子周圍有很多手機
you can put them in your kitchen your
你可以把它們放在你的廚房裡
living room your dining room your
客廳你的餐廳你的
bedroom wherever you like and it will
臥室，無論你喜歡什麼， 它會
all operate off one of the devices I'm
所有的設備都是我操作的
pretty familiar with with these devices
非常熟悉這些設備
viewers if you've never worked with with
觀眾，如果你從未與之合作過
a net talk device before what you can
你可以在之前使用網絡通話設備
actually do what I've done at home is I
實際做我在家做的就是我
went out to my garage where the phone
我的 車庫裡出了電話
service comes in right my phone lines
服務進入我的電話線
already like they carry power if you
已經像他們攜帶電源，如果你
plug in your phone even if you don't
即使你不插電話也要插上電話
have service you can hear that there's
有服務，你可以聽到 有
power on the line right so you've got
在線路上的電源，所以你有
five bolts going through at all times so
五個螺栓始終貫穿所以
I snipped the cable okay so that now
我現在剪斷電纜 好了
that my phone lines in the house are
我家裡的電話線是
completely dead right I get my nettalk
完全死了我得到了我的nettalk
duo to and i plug this into any one of
duo to和i將其插入任何一個
the phone jacks in my house right as
我家裡的電話插孔就像
long as you have a dead jack long as
只要你有一個死去的傑克長
it's dead as long as it's dead it has
它已經死了，只要它已經死了
like a task right it has to be dead you
就像一項任務一樣，它必須要死你
can do that and you can get you can I
能做到這一點，你可以得到你我
end up using the dead jacks all over the
最終全部採用死千斤頂在
house when you do it that way as opposed
當你這樣做的時候反對
to going with a wireless phone set so I
跟我一起去無線電話
have a couple of wireless phones but I
我有幾個無線電話
also I'm a little old school I have a
我也是一個古老的小學校
wired phone hanging in my kitchen
有線電話掛在我的廚房裡
plugged into the jack just like right am
像上午一樣插入插孔
I used to have right so it's pretty
我曾經沒錯，所以很漂亮
awesome so it's like having phone
真棒，所以就像打電話一樣
service the traditional style phone
服務傳統風格的手機
service but it manages to nettalk are
服務，但它設法nettalk是
I've got unlimited 15 bits off it's
我有無限的15位
unlimited I'm not talking on the phone
無限我不是在打電話
for 1500 minutes a month okay okay
一個月1500分鐘沒關係好吧
that's unlimited okay it's unlimited if
這是無限的，如果是無限的
you got teenagers maybe not how much is
你有青少年也許不是多少
1500 minutes if you'd have a hard time
如果你有困難， 1500分鐘
going through it I'm in Canada where can
經歷它我在加拿大哪裡可以
I call you can call the US you can add
我打電話給你可以打電話給 你可以添加 的 美國
international minutes you can you know
國際會議紀要你知道嗎
you can call anywhere and there's no
你可以在任何地方打電話，但沒有
long distance charges at all there's no
所有的長途費用都沒有
monthly fees except overseas except
除海外以外的月費
overseas right you can add international
海外權利，你可以添加國際
minutes for that maybe the vet the rates
分鐘可能是獸醫的費率
vary depending on where you want to call
根據您要撥打的電話而有所不同
it's quite reasonable and it's totally
這是非常合理的，而且完全是
reasonable and yeah you can call no long
合理，是的，你可以打電話不久
distance charges at all there's no
所有的距離收費都沒有
monthly fees you pay for the device at
您為該設備支付的月費
at retailer line when you buy it and
在零售商行購買時
that's your cost and then you just face
這是你的成本然後你只是面對
a renewal cost that's it so what
更新成本就是這樣
must be like two hundred dollars right
一定要兩百美元吧
Nelson no no no the way I mean the
尼爾森不，不，我的意思是
renewal is a fifth like 50 bucks a year
續約是五分之一，每年50美元
that's it and I've got unlimited calling
就是這樣，我有無限的召喚
essentially anywhere in Canada us so one
基本上在加拿大我們這麼一個地方
of the things that's really cool about
那些非常酷的事情
this beyond being able to hook it into
除了能夠將其掛鉤之外
my home phone as i mentioned i can take
我提到的家用電話我可以帶
this anywhere i go if you're a traveler
如果你是 一個旅行者， 我會去的任何地方
or if you've got kids that have gone
或者如果你有孩子已經離開了
away for school or something like that
去學校或類似的東西
so this little device packed in a bag
所以這個小裝置裝在一個袋子裡
along with a phone becomes a local phone
隨著手機成為本地手機
call for anyone so that's right if I
呼籲任何人，所以這是正確的，如果我
activate this here in Barrie Ontario
在Barrie Ontario這裡激活它
with a Barrie Ontario number right like
與巴里安大略省的號碼一樣
and then I go down to the states for
然後我去到 了美國
school or for work or whatever I still
學校或工作或我還在做什麼
have a Barrie Ontario number right and
有一個Barrie安大略省號碼和
anybody in bahria can call you wherever
bahria的任何人都可以在任何地方給你打電話
you are and it'll it'll be all right and
你是，它會它會沒事 的 ，並
it'll be totally for free absolute from
它絕對是完全免費的
their cell phone absolutely self yeah
他們的手機絕對是自己的
it's not a long-distance call so if you
這不是長途電話，所以如果你
travel a lot you can actually pack it in
經常旅行你可以把它裝進去
your suitcase take it with you if I was
如果我的話，你的行李箱隨身攜帶
overseas so if I've activated this in
海外，所以如果我已激活這
Canada and I've gone overseas now I can
加拿大和我現在已經出國了
call home to Canada for free or the US
免費致電加拿大或美國
or the US right and they could vice
或美國的權利，他們卻是副
versa they could call you and then and
相反，他們可以打電話給你，然後和
the device thinks it's where where was
設備認為它就在哪裡
that where was that where it was
那是哪裡的地方
activated with it with the area code
使用區號激活它
that's on it yeah i mean that's that's
就是它，是的，我的意思是那就是
the beauty of this is the world we're
這就是我們所擁有的世界
living in folks so in cut the cord
生活在鄉親這樣切斷了繩子
cutting the cord is so much easier when
切割電線時更容易
you can do stuff like this and it's
你可以做這樣的事情吧
you're not tied down to any chord any
你沒有受到任何和弦的束縛
any internet connection you can take it
任何互聯網連接，你可以採取它
in right all you need to do is like
在所有你需要做的就是
we've got you know plug it into the
我們已經讓你知道插入它
router or don't play if you have the
如果你有路由器或不玩
Wi-Fi device plug it in anywhere in your
Wi-Fi設備將其插入您的任何地方
house you don't need the router you just
你不需要路由器的房子
set you know you just put your Wi-Fi
設置你知道你只是把你的Wi-Fi
settings into it just like you would
像你一樣設置它
your laptop so for me at home the
你的筆記本電腦對我來說在家裡
nettalk duo two is the right choice
nettalk duo two是正確的選擇
because I've got ethernet and i just
因為我有以太網， 我只是
plug it into the router and that's fine
把它插入路由器，沒關係
but what just struck me is if i was
但令我印象深刻的是，如果我是
traveling some hotels will not have
旅行一些酒店將不會
ethernet they'll be Wi-Fi only so then
以太網，他們只會是Wi-Fi
so that's when you take the dot do a
這就是你拿點做的時候
Wi-Fi with you you want and you can use
隨心所欲地使用 Wi-Fi，您可以使用
it just plug it into your laptop and
它只是插入你的筆記本電腦和
away you go where you don't have to do
離開你去你不需要做的地方
you know you could just connect it to
你知道你可以把它連接到
their Wi-Fi oh yeah connect it to the
他們的Wi-Fi哦，是的，它連接到
law you have to set you get the Wi-Fi to
法律你必須 設置你獲得Wi-Fi
get the Wi-Fi yeah okay yeah and then
得到Wi-Fi是的好，是的，然後
they're at standalone yep very cool yeah
他們是獨立的，非常酷，是的
so those are the devices and you know
所以這些是設備，你知道
you've you've proven the the product and
你已經證明了產品和產品
it's been fantastic and reliable as you
它和你一樣美妙可靠
mentioned it's about it was a fifty
提到它是關於它是一個五十
dollars per year and I get all yeah yeah
每年美元，我得到所有是啊是的
well the prices in Canada are in Canada
以及加拿大的價格都在加拿大
so right little less in the States so
所以在美國這麼少
the duo the duo sells for 5995 the duo
兩人組合出售5995雙人組合
two is 4495 and the duo Wi-Fi is 7495
兩個是4495， 二人Wi-Fi是7495
and that includes time and everything's
這包括時間和一切
that includes your first year do you get
包括你的第一年， 你明白
like voicemail called the voicemail call
就像語音郵件一樣叫做語音郵件
display call forwarding call answer all
顯示呼叫轉移呼叫應答全部
the bells and whistles that a normal
正常的鈴聲和口哨聲
telco company would give you our
電信公司會給你我們的
included in this device that's awesome
包含在這個設備中真棒
cool okay so let's move on from the
很酷， 所以讓我們繼續前進吧
devices because you guys have spent the
設備，因為你們已經花了
last couple of years now revolutionising
最近幾年 正在徹底改革
your services we've we've all been quite
你們的服務我們一直都很好
concerned over the past you know a
關注過去你知道嗎
couple years about security and
幾年來關於安全和
realizing that our privacy is not isn't
意識到我們的隱私不是
it's not real yeah and so you know even
這不是真的，所以你甚至都知道
from my cell phone or my my phone I'm
從我的手機或我的手機我
worried about getting intercepted
擔心被截獲
messages people sniffing my messages and
消息人們嗅探我的消息和
things so what is that I understand that
事情那麼我理解的是什麼
talk is working to improve the situation
談話正在努力改善這種狀況
there are platforms like blackberry
有像黑莓這樣的平台
comes to mind where I'm not really sure
浮現在我不確定的地方
where they're going to be in five years
他們五年後會在哪裡
mhm mmm so what is nettalk doing to step
嗯mmm nettalk做什麼步驟
up and say okay here is something that
起來，說這裡好吧
we can offer this kind well we've got a
我們可以提供這種井， 我們有一個
we've got a brand new connect messaging
我們有一個全新的連接消息
app is a private secure fully encrypted
應用程序是完全加密的私有安全
app it gives you added security and this
應用程序，它為您提供了額外的安全性
is this is a messaging like chat or like
這是一個 像聊天或類似 的消息
text messaging or yeah so that that
短信或是的，以便那樣
keeps your messaging very very secure
保持您的消息非常安全
you were talking about security so that
你是在談論安全問題
yeah my thinking now I was reading about
是的，我現在的想法，我正在閱讀
this this service and it sounds like
這項服務聽起來像
you've got like a proxy setup and and
你有一個代理設置和
VPN tunneling from my phone to the proxy
從我的手機到代理的VPN隧道
so that everything is absolutely
所以一切都是絕對的
encrypted and writer so as I'm sending
加密和寫作，所以我發送
texts man
文本人
is from my phone app so not through my
來自我的手機應用程序所以不是通過我的
phone itself through text message
通過短信給自己打電話
through the app than that talk app yeah
通過應用程序比談話應用程序是的
then I'm able to send it encrypted and
然後我就能 加密發送它了
it's going to be a lot safer than
它會比安全更安全
abscess ending absolutely and we've got
膿腫絕對結束，我們得到了
another app that i was mentioning the
我提到的另一個應用程序
kinect talk app that that app works with
該應用程序使用的kinect talk應用程序
Wi-Fi LTE 4G LTE okay and and there's no
Wi-Fi LTE 4G LTE還可以，而且沒有
roaming charges you can so this is
漫遊收費你可以這樣做
actual phone calls right through my
實際的電話通過我的電話
phone through the app yep so if i
電話通過應用程序是的，如果我
install this app can i make phone calls
安裝此應用程序， 我可以撥打電話
over Wi-Fi yes absolutely Wi-Fi 3G 4G
通過Wi-Fi是絕對的Wi-Fi 3G 4G
LTE so what that means see I think about
LTE所以這意味著我 想到了
my cell phone if I go over the border
我的手機，如果我越過邊境
and I'm instantly paying roaming fees
我立即支付漫遊費
right I'm instantly having to pay a huge
對，我馬上要付出巨額代價
long distance right call home right with
長途右轉呼叫回家權利
net talk i can now download the app i
net talk我現在可以下載app了
hate to sound like a tella like I'm
討厭像我一樣聽起來像一個傢伙
trying to get my head around this but
試圖讓我的 頭 圍繞這一點，但
you guys have been doing so much to to
你們這麼做了
better the service and make it more
更好的服務，使其更多
accessible on the cell phone so even
手機上訪問所以即使
without these devices now I've got these
沒有這些設備現在我有這些
apps to supplement right are they
應用程序補充權利是他們
interconnected is my device at home
互聯是家裡的設備
going to be connected yeah all is all
將要連接是的一切都是
through an all through one platform
通過一個通過一個平台
everything yeah one platform covers the
一切都是平台覆蓋的
whole thing it is then does the number
那麼整個事情就是這個數字
on my cell phone stay the same or how
在我的手機上保持不變或如何
does that work um I yeah I believe so
這有用嗎我是的我相信
yes and you get it you get an app number
是的，你得到它你得到一個應用程序號碼
as well so the app itself has a separate
以及應用程序本身有一個單獨的
phone number yeah local color yeah
電話號碼是啊當地的顏色是的
that's cool yeah very cool yeah what are
這很酷，是的非常酷，是的
the Rosario working on the net time
羅薩里奧在淨時間工作
we've got thing about cell phones well
我們有關於手機的事情
we've got a cut we've got a connect on
我們有一個削減，我們有一個連接
4G sim card that has to be it's really
4G sim卡必須是真的
good because it it allows you to use
好，因為它可以讓 你使用
your service we've got you're bringing
您的服務，我們已經得到了你把
out sim cards yep like a net talk sim
出來的SIM卡就像網絡通話一樣
card yeah it's a it's well it's not it's
卡是的，它很好，它不是它
it's a sim card connect on 4G it's the
這是一張連接4G的SIM卡
nation's fastest and lowest cost nation
全國成本最快，成本最低的國家
4G LTE network now available and it's
現在可以使用4G LTE網絡了
got a special price on it right now for
得到它一個特殊的價格現在為
twenty dollars a month
一個月二十美元
first five months and then it goes to 40
前五個月，然後到40
and sir it's one plan one price so no
先生，這是一個計劃一個價格所以沒有
contract yep numbers don't matter to me
合同是的，對我來說無關緊要
but right okay I mean I I know you guys
但是沒錯， 我的意思是我認識你們
are affordable 20 bucks 30 apps for cell
是負擔得起20塊錢的30個應用程序的細胞
service so you're talking you can get a
服務，所以你說你可以得到一個
sim card for my cell phone that does it
用於我的手機的SIM卡
have the same sort of similar services
有 類似的類似服務
to net talk or you what what services
網談或者你有什麼服務
come with that so it's unlimited talk
來吧，這是無限的談話
text and data unlimited yep and no
文本和數據無限制，沒有
there's much no additional sorry now the
現在還有很多不好意思了
numbers matter twenty dollars a month
數字每月二十美元
for the first five months and then forty
對於前五個月 ，然後40
dollars after that is the regular price
之後的美元是 正常價格
it's already luxe a month right so right
這個月已經很奢侈了
now it's on special it has to be
現在它必須是特殊的
activated in the United States okay and
在美國激活好了
it's good for Canada Mexico Puerto Rico
這對加拿大墨西哥波多黎各有好處
up to 10 gigabytes of data and what
高達10千兆字節的數據和什麼
happens after 10 gigs it's my phone stop
發生10次演出後，我的手機停了下來
accessing the internet no no not at all
訪問互聯網無無不是在 所有
i think it's just a little order to pay
我認為這只是一個小訂單
more I probably just pay more but pretty
更多我可能只是支付更多但很漂亮
but pretty hard to go to 10 gigs so I
但 很難去10場演出，所以 我
don't think that's a problem okay so
不要以為這是 一個問題 好了，
we've got LTE service unlimited up to 10
我們的LTE服務最多可達10個
gigs hmm so that's limited but it's an
嘻嘻嗯所以這是有限的，但它是一個
affordable service it's like 40 bucks
價格實惠的服務就像40美元一樣
for that so a sim card allows me to now
為此，一張SIM卡可以讓我現在
take a like a pay-as-you-go phone and I
我喜歡像手機一樣的電話
can pop a SIM card into that yeah you
可以彈出一個SIM 卡插入 你呀
just need an ani provide unlocked phone
只需要ani提供解鎖手機
it has to be activated in the United
它必須在美國激活
States but it'll work on all those
國家，但它將適用於所有這些
countries so once it's activated in the
這些國家一旦被激活了
US it can be where it can be used in any
美國它可以 在任何 地方 使用
of the other countries so you couldn't
其他國家，所以你不能
order it on a Canadian can't order it
在加拿大訂購它不能訂購它
online and have it delivered into Canada
在線並將其發送到加拿大
and activated in Canada it can't be
並且在加拿大激活它不可能
activated in Canada first it has to be
首先必須在加拿大激活
activated in the United States though
雖然在美國激活
the the service is available here but I
這個服務在這裡，但我
have to get it activated down there
必須在那裡激活它
right I'd have to either travel to the
對，我要去旅行
states right or maybe send it to a relat
陳述權利或者可能將其發送給相關人士
but maybe if you want to buy it send it
但也許如果你想買它發送它
to a relative have them activated for
一個親戚激活他們
you and then coming from the rep right
你然後來自代表權利
so is that okay like do they frown on
他們皺眉頭也好
that um I haven't heard any problems in
我沒有聽到任何問題
doing that and then I haven't have them
這樣做，然後我沒有他們
sent up here how I mean unless you
發送到這裡我的意思除非你
travel to the US and buy it directly
前往美國並直接購買
right so you can order it
對，所以你可以訂購它
up here okay so this is so we're to
在這裡好吧所以我們這樣做
speaking with Nelson who does from from
與來自Nelson的Nelson交談
net talk and net talk is a really great
網絡談話和網絡談話真的很棒
way to replace your phone service and
更換手機服務的方法
we've talked about the home phone
我們談到了家庭電話
service and being able to cut the cord
服務和能夠切斷電源線
and and and replace that with a device
和，並用設備替換它
like this that's going to give you full
像這樣會給你滿滿的
phone service at home for eastern n jug
東部n jug的家庭電話服務
in with the ethernet cord plug it into
用以太網線插入
the wall for power or plug it it you
電源牆或插電你
know and now speaking of cutting the
知道， 現在說切割
cord looking at their cell phone and
繩子看著他們的手機和
you're offering not just apps but a sim
你不僅提供應用程序，還提供SIM卡
card that will actually provide our
實際上會提供我們的卡
service right so this must be third
服務權，所以這必須是第三
party service yeah it's it's using
派對服務是的， 它正在使用
t-mobile network in the US and Bell
美國和貝爾的移動網絡
Rogers and Telus in Canada okay so all
加拿大的 Rogers和Telus 都可以
big name mobile providers so yeah so I
大名鼎鼎的 移動提供商 所以是的，所以我
mean check them out we can go to net
意思是檢查出來我們可以去網
talk dot CA if you're in Canada if
如果你在加拿大，請談談CA
you're in the United States is there
你在美國 是有
more information about the the cellular
有關細胞的更多信息
service in the states i guess because
在各州服務我猜是因為
that's where it's based yeah its own
這就是它自己的基礎
daughter netcom nettalk calm is the US
女兒網通nettalk 平靜是 美國
website net talk dot CA is the canadian
網站net talk dot CA是加拿大人
website for canadians okay so check that
加拿大人的網站好吧所以檢查一下
out nettalk calm is where you want to go
nettalk平靜是你想去的地方
for if you're interested in the cell
因為如果你對細胞感興趣的話
service and if you're in canada net talk
服務，如果你在加拿大網絡談話
dot CA now these devices are fantastic
dot CA現在這些設備非常棒
and and they do work very very well and
而且他們的工作非常好
so we want to offer our viewers an
所以我們想為觀眾提供一個
opportunity to to win some one of these
有機會贏得其中一些
so we've got a handful to give away
所以我們有一把放棄了
absolutely than kind of surrounding me
絕對不是周圍的我
here yeah so we're going to give you
在這裡，所以我們要給你
various ways to win over the next couple
贏得下一對夫婦的各種方式
of weeks but certainly if you are a
幾週，但肯定如果你是一個
supporter on patreon you're going to be
帕特雷恩的支持者你將成為
first up and you've got a chance with
首先，你有機會
with really good odds there on patreon
帕特雷恩的賠率非常高
right now to pick up one of these
現在就拿起 其中的 一個
nettalk devices so which which are we
nettalk設備，這是我們的
given away we're giving away the nettalk
放棄我們贈送nettalk
duo two duo two that's the one I've got
二人二人這是我得到的那個
all right and that has believed in
沒事，而且相信了
Canada we've got three months of service
加拿大我們有三個月的服務期
on that and a great great great great
在那上面，偉大偉大的偉大
product so you get the device for free
產品讓您免費獲得該設備
if you win and get three months of free
如果你獲勝並獲得三個月的免費
phone service activated in Canada or the
電話服務在加拿大或
US yep
美國是的
and and then from there it's forty or
然後從那裡它四十或
fifty forty dollars us or fifty dollars
五十四美元我們或五十美元
Canadian right want to you know you've
加拿大的權利想要你知道你
evaluated the service and then you can
評估服務然後你可以
give it a try for three months it if you
如果你， 試試 三個月吧
like it you can do will yeah you can you
喜歡它， 你能做到的，是的，你可以
can keep going cool so patreon
可以保持冷靜，所以Patreon
supporters you're going to be first up
支持者，你將成為第一個
on that we're going to give you the
我們會給你的
information make sure you check out our
信息確保你看看我們的
patreon page patreon.com/lenguin you're
patreon page patreon.com/lenguin你
branching into of the cellular market
進入細胞市場
because of progressively more and more
因為越來越多
people are switching to their cell
人們正在轉向他們的細胞
phones as their home yeah the landline
電話作為他們的家是的固定電話
is do I mean the landline is dead if I
我的意思是，如果我，固定電話已經死了
mean if it's if it's not totally dead
意味著，如果它不是完全死了
yet it probably will be pretty soon like
但很可能很快就會這樣
you know what's next I can't give away
你知道接下來我不能放棄的是什麼
all of our secrets Robbie come on you
我們所有的秘密都羅比來找你
know but the you know the the fact that
知道，但你知道的事實
we're into the apps in this uh you know
我們進入這個應用程序 你知道嗎？
the SIM cards later service is just an
SIM卡以後的服務只是一個
extension of what we do here with the
延伸我們在這裡做的事情
devices very good so check those out
設備非常好，所以檢查出來
nettalk dot CA in Canada or nettalk calm
nettalk dot CA在加拿大或nettalk平靜
if you're in the United States Nelson
如果你在美國尼爾森
it's always a pleasure to have you here
讓你來到這裡總是很高興
appreciate you making the trip to come
感謝你 來這裡 旅行
and see us my pleasure my pleasure and I
並且看到我們很高興和我一起享受
encourage you to do check out that talk
鼓勵你 看看 這些傳言
welcome back this is category five
歡迎回來這是第五類
technology TV thanks to our guest
科技電視感謝我們的客人
tonight Nelson who does make sure you
今晚尼爾森確實幫了你
check them out at net talk dot CA in
在net talk dot CA中查看它們
Canada neta com if you are in the United
加拿大 neta com，如果你在 美國
States very cool stuff they're doing and
陳述他們正在做的非常酷的事情
don't forget we are giving away some of
不要忘記我們正在放棄一些
those so make sure you checked out on
那些，所以請確保你簽出
patreon cat5 TV / patreon to be one of
patreon cat5 TV / patreon是其中之一
the first to qualify for that for that
第一晉級 ，對於該
draw and we do have a handful to give
畫畫，我們確實有一把給予
away but as as there are many fewer
離開，但因為有更少
patreon supporters than there are
帕特雷恩的支持者比有
viewers yes your odds of winning on
觀眾是您獲勝的機率
patreon are much higher than once we
帕特雷恩比我們高出一倍
open it up to all the views okay so
把它打開所有的觀點好吧
that's how that works so make sure you
這是如何工作所以確保你
check that out cat5 TV / patreon and
檢查出cat5 TV / patreon和
thanks to you she'll for being here
謝謝你，她會在這裡
thanks for being here Robbie I know
謝謝你在這里羅比，我知道
right nice to be here as always fighting
很高興能像往常一樣在這裡戰鬥
us every week you know ya gotta do
我們每週你都知道你必須這樣做
something with my Tuesday night they
他週二晚上的事情
want to be bored no you just keep coming
想要無聊，不管你不斷來
back what else am I gonna do we love you
回到我還能做什麼我們愛你
for it yeah thanks and we love you for
因為它是的，謝謝，我們愛你
being here thank you so much for joining
在這裡非常感謝你的加入
us tonight and we will catch you again
我們今晚， 我們會 再次抓住你
next Tuesday nights in place same time
下週二晚上同時到位
of great week night arrivederci
偉大的一周的晚上到達